export const Question21to30 = [
    {
        Question: "What is Vercel?",
        Options: ['A version control system', 'A cloud platform for static sites and Serverless Functions', 'A programming language', 'A database management system'],
        Answer: "A cloud platform for static sites and Serverless Functions"
    },
    {
        Question: "Which command is used to deploy a project on Vercel?",
        Options: ['vercel deploy', 'git push', 'npm start', 'vercel init'],
        Answer: "vercel deploy"
    },
    {
        Question: "What is the primary language used for configuration in Vercel?",
        Options: ['JSON', 'YAML', 'XML', 'HTML'],
        Answer: "JSON"
    },
    {
        Question: "What is the default branch that Vercel uses for deployments?",
        Options: ['main', 'master', 'deploy', 'production'],
        Answer: "main"
    },
    {
        Question: "What feature does Vercel provide for previewing changes before deploying to production?",
        Options: ['Preview Deployments', 'Staging Branch', 'Test Mode', 'Snapshot View'],
        Answer: "Preview Deployments"
    },
    {
        Question: "Which framework is tightly integrated with Vercel for optimal performance?",
        Options: ['Next.js', 'Angular', 'Vue.js', 'Svelte'],
        Answer: "Next.js"
    },
    {
        Question: "What is the purpose of the 'vercel.json' file?",
        Options: ['To configure deployment settings', 'To list project dependencies', 'To manage user authentication', 'To handle environment variables'],
        Answer: "To configure deployment settings"
    },
    {
        Question: "What type of hosting does Vercel specialize in?",
        Options: ['Static site hosting', 'Managed database hosting', 'Virtual private servers', 'Content delivery network'],
        Answer: "Static site hosting"
    },
    {
        Question: "What is the CLI command to initialize a new Vercel project?",
        Options: ['vercel init', 'vercel start', 'vercel create', 'vercel new'],
        Answer: "vercel init"
    },
    {
        Question: "Which feature of Vercel allows for server-side rendering and API routes?",
        Options: ['Serverless Functions', 'Edge Caching', 'Static Exports', 'Client-side Rendering'],
        Answer: "Serverless Functions"
    }
];
